codeforest.net 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy - CodeForest

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to [contact us](https://www.codeforest.net/contact).

At codeforest.net, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by codeforest.net and how it is used.

## Cookies and Web Beacons

Like many websites, codeforest.net uses cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

Some of our advertising, social media and analytics partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our partners include Google (AdSense, Analytics, Google+), Disqus and Facebook.

These third-party servers or networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on codeforest.net send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the content that you see.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party networks for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. condeforest.net’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

You can find Google’s privacy policy here: [How Google uses data when you use our partners’ sites or apps.](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/)

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites. You may also opt out of the use of the Google’s DoubleClick cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting [Ads Settings](http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/).

## Log Files

Like many websites, codeforest.net makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.
